<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.kyarorukyo.hyprlandsettings</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <name>Hyprland Settings</name>
  <summary>Review and safely edit supported Hyprland settings</summary>
  <developer id="io.github.kyarorukyo">
    <name>KYO</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>Hyprland Settings is a GTK/libadwaita application for browsing official Hyprland setting metadata, reviewing the active config layout, using guarded reversible runtime previews, and applying drift-safe atomic saves for supported settings.</p>
    <p>The current implementation exposes 290 of 341 scalar rows, supports fresh-absence insertion for eligible missing settings, and persists proven existing Animation and Bezier Curve records. It keeps 51 high-risk scalar rows, duplicate auto-resolution, five other structured families, and profile/mode activation blocked.</p>
    <p>The bundled metadata targets Hyprland 0.55.2. This app is not an official Hyprland project.</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.kyarorukyo.hyprlandsettings.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/KyaroruKYO/hyprland-settings</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Settings</category>
    <category>GTK</category>
  </categories>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
    <release version="0.2.0" date="2026-07-13">
      <description>
        <p>Runtime-first live preview with supervised dead-man recovery, Safe Live Save Mode gating every save, gated single-write persistence with byte-exact backups and reread verification, a structured-family record picker for proven animation and bezier record shapes (enabled, speed, and existing-curve references), and a Hyprland 0.55.4 zero-drift compatibility audit.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release type="development" version="0.2.0~rc.1" date="2026-07-13">
      <description>
        <p>Release candidate: runtime-first live preview with supervised dead-man recovery, Safe Live Save Mode gating every save, gated single-write persistence with byte-exact backups and reread verification, a structured-family record picker for proven animation and bezier record shapes, and a Hyprland 0.55.4 zero-drift compatibility audit.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.1.0" date="2026-06-19">
      <description>
        <p>First release: read-only browsing of official Hyprland setting metadata with guarded safe-batch config writes for eligible normal scalar settings.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
